Guide to the James B. Hunt Papers
James B. Hunt Papers
- Videotape, 1980-1984, 1987-1997, and undated
  - Hard Drive of Digitized Materials, 2010 (Box 65)
- Film, 1984, 1996, and undated
  This series primarily contains Super 16 film reels. Many reels appear to be fragmentary in nature, and feature raw footage intended to be edited into television commercials, although the exact relationships are often unclear. Transcripts and cue sheets for some of this material may be found in Series 5.
  - DHS Films - Hunt - 16mm Mag. Scratch Mix, 1984 January 30 (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - 16mm Mag. VO Trims, 1984 January-February (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Spots (Together :30 & :60, Working People :30 & :60, Farmer :30) - Music, 1984 February 1 (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Working People :30 & :60 only (without music) mixed trk, 1984 February 1 (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Spots (Together :30 & :60, Working People :30 & :60, Farmer :30) - Music, 1984 February 1 (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Spots (Together :30 & :60, Working People :30 & :60, Farmer :30) - Narr. Track, 1984 February 1 (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Spots (Together :30 & :60, Working People :30 & :60, Farmer :30) - unlabeled, 1984 February 1 (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Spots (Together :30 and :60, Working People :30 and :60, Farmer :30) A-Roll, 1984 February 1 (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Spots (Together :30 and :60, Working People :30 and :60, Farmer :30) B-Roll, 1984 February 1 (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Spots - Mix Elements (Future :60, Motive :30 - All the People) Narr., Fx, Mixed Mag., 1984 February 8 (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - 3 Rough (Test) Hunt Spots - Mix Elements (Enemies, Who's He Fighting For?, Pride) - Mixed Mag./1/4" safety (Music on Dial A) 245-0047, 1984 April 28 (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Bookstore/County Fair", 1984 October 3 (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Bookstore/County Fair", 1984 October 3 (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Speech" Code CE & CF Sync Pix, 1984 October 3 (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Speech" Code CE & CF Sync Trk, 1984 October 3 (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Speech Testimonials" Code CB Sync Pix, 1984 October 3 (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Speech Testimonials" Neg Cut, 1984 October 3 (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Speech Testimonials" Code CB Sync Trk, 1984 October 3 (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Wild Track (Continuations of Tks.) - Not Coded, 1984 October 3 (Box 30)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Testimonials" Code CB0000, SR 3,4,5; Tks 4,7,8,9,34 (3 slates), AR #20 Sync Trk, 1984 October 3 (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Testimonials" Code CB0000, CR 5,6,9,10; Tks 4,7,8,9,34 (3 slates), AR #20 Sync Pix, 1984 October 3 (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "County Fair Part 1" Code CC0000 AR#21 Sync Pix, 1984 October 3 (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "County Fair Part 1" Code CC0000 AR#21 Sync Trk, 1984 October 3 (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Speech in Auditorium Part 1" Code CE0000 SR6 Takes 34-37 AR#23 Sync Trk, 1984 October 3 (Box 35)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Speech in Auditorium Part 1" Code CE0000 SR6 Takes 34-37 AR#23 Sync Pix, 1984 October 3 (Box 35)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "County Fair Part 2" Code CD0000 Takes 27-32 CR8,9 AR#22 Sync Pix, 1984 October 3 (Box 35)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "County Fair Part 2" Code CD0000 Takes 27-32 CR8,9 AR#22 Sync Trk, 1984 October 3 (Box 35)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Hunt at Factory" Code CA0000 CR1,2,3 TK1-3 AR#19 Sync Trk, 1984 October 3 (Box 35)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Hunt at Factory" Code CA0000 CR1,2,3 TK1-3 AR#19 Sync Pix, 1984 October 3 (Box 35)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Bookstore/Street" Code CG0000 AR#25 Sync Trk, 1984 October 3 (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Bookstore/Street" Code CG0000 AR#25 Sync Pix, 1984 October 3 (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #1 - M-237-7621 -- M-237-8414, 1984 October 4 (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #1 - D-489-8920 -- D-489-9653, 1984 October 4 (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #1 - S-974-0954 -- S974-1747, 1984 October 4 (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Testimonials - Helms" Mixed Mag. 1/4" Safety Mix, 1984 October 12 (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Testimonial - Helms" Original Color Negative A-roll, 1984 October 12 (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Testimonial - Helms" Original Color Negative B-roll, 1984 October 12 (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - A-I in (HD) & Out, TL VO Hunt, 1984 October 16 (Box 30)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress" VO A-I Outs, 1984 October 16 (Box 30)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - VO "Progress :60" Revised, 1984 October 17 (Box 30)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Narr. Outs "Progress :60", 1984 October 18 (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Narr. Outs "Progress :60" Final Version, 1984 October 19 (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :60" 1/4" 15 ips Mix, 1984 October 19 (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :30", 1984 October 22 (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :30" Retransfer, 1984 October 22 (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :30" A-Roll Negative, 1984 October 24 (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :30" B-Roll Negative, 1984 October 24 (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :30" Mixed Mag. 1/4"15ips safety, 1984 October 24 (Box 30)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :30" Narr. Track, 1984 October 24 (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :30" Music (Alt) Track B, 1984 October 24 (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "The Choice" Music Track, 1984 October 24 (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :30" Narr. Track, 1984 October 24 (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "The Choice" :30 Mix, 1984 October 26 (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - Original Color Negative (Single Strand), 1984 November 1 (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Silhouette" from AR#12 Pix, 1984 (Box 30)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Silhouette" from AR#12 Trk, 1984 (Box 30)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Hunt Interview Part 3"/"Fiscal Meeting Part 1" 245.0047 AR#12 BD0000- Pix, 1984 (Box 31)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Hunt Interview Part 3"/"Fiscal Meeting Part 1" 245.0047 AR#12 BD0000- Trk, 1984 (Box 31)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 1, 2, 3 7293 ECN Original WO#18486 Tail, 1996 March 27 (Flatbox 44)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 4, 5, 6 7293 ECN Original #18486 Tail, 1996 March 28 (Flatbox 44)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 13. 14. 15 7293 Ecn Orginianl #18486 Tail, 1996 March 28 (Flatbox 44)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 16. 17. 18 7293, 93, 45 ECN Original #18486 Tail, 1996 March 28 (Flatbox 44)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 10, 11, 12 7293 ECN Original #18486 Tail, 1996 March 28 (Flatbox 45)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 7, 8, 9 7293 ECN Original #18486 Tail, 1996 March 28 (Flatbox 45)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 1, 2, 3 7293 ECN Original WO#20233 Tail, 1996 August 14 (Flatbox 46)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 4, 5, 6 7293 ECN Original #20233 Tail, 1996 August 14 (Flatbox 46)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 7, 8, 9 ECN 7293 #20233 Tail, 1996 August 14 (Flatbox 47)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 10, 11, 12 ECN 7293, 79, 93 #20233 Tail, 1996 August 14 (Flatbox 47)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 13, 14 7293 ECN Original WO#20233 Tail, 1996 August 14 (Flatbox 48)
  - GMMB - "Hunt" - CR# 15, 16 7293 ECN Original WO#20233 Tail, 1996 August 14 (Flatbox 48)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Press Conference Pix Code: AC0000-, undated (Box 24)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Press Conference Trk Code: AC0000-, undated (Box 24)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Farm Part 2" Pix Code: AB0000-, undated (Box 24)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Farm Part 2" Trk Code: AB0000-, undated (Box 24)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Farm Part 1" Trk Code AA0000-, undated (Box 24)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Farm Part 1" Pix Code AA0000-, undated (Box 24)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Porch Couple Part 1" Pix Code: AD0000-, undated (Box 24)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Porch Couple Part 1" Trk Code: AD0000-, undated (Box 24)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Music Track of :60 Hunt Progress, undated (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Narration - "The Choice", undated (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Narration - "Helms", undated (Box 25)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Office" Pix, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Office" Trk, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Shots of Working People" Trk, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Equal Opportunity Assembly", undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Equal Opportunity Assembly" Lift, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Faces" Neg. Cut, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - Bin Selects & Trims, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Factory" Trk, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Factory" Pix, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Couples Meeting" Pix, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Couples Meeting" Trk, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Fiscal Meeting" Trk, undated (Box 26)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Black Couple, Principal, Elderly Principal, Guidance Counselor" Trk, undated (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Black Couple, Principal, Elderly Principal, Guidance Counselor" Pix, undated (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Mrs. Hunt" Pix, undated (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Mrs. Hunt" Trk, undated (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Interview" Neg Cut, undated (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Hunt Interview" Trk, undated (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Hunt Interview" Pix, undated (Box 27)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Kids in Library" Pix, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Kids in Library" Trk, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - Glenn MOS shots used in Hunt spots, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Farm" Sync Pix, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Farm" Sync Trk, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Fiscal Meeting" Pix, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Aide Testimonial" Pix, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Aide Testimonial" Trk, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "General Store Testimonial" Pix, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "General Store Testimonial" Trk, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Old Couple Testimonial (Porch Couple)" Sync Pix, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Old Couple Testimonial (Porch Couple)" Sync Trk, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Mill" Sync Trk, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Mill" Sync Pix, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Mill" Neg Cut (Dupe), undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Lumber Yard, Mechanic and Wife, Young Man Testimonial" Sync Pix, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - "Lumber Yard, Mechanic and Wife, Young Man Testimonial" Sync Trk, undated (Box 28)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Inauguration Dupe Pix (1 of 2), undated (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Inauguration Dupe Pix (2 of 2), undated (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - 1st Shoot Negative Testimonials and Selects - Pix, undated (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Selects - 1st Shoot Negative Testimonials and Selects - Trk, undated (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - Track Music (Not Used) - Beg. Of Grasslands 2x's, Dixie, undated (Box 29)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Kids in Library Part 2," "Couples Meeting" 245.0047, AR#16, BH0000-, Pix, undated (Box 30)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Kids in Library Part 2," "Couples Meeting" 245.0047, AR#16, BH0000-, Trk, undated (Box 30)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Fiscal Meeting Part 2," "Aide Testimonial" Pix, undated (Box 31)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Fiscal Meeting Part 2," "Aide Testimonial" Trk, undated (Box 31)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Black Couple, School Principal" Pix, undated (Box 31)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Black Couple, School Principal" Trk, undated (Box 31)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Principal, Elderly Principal, Guidance Counselor" Pix, undated (Box 31)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Principal, Elderly Principal, Guidance Counselor" Trk, undated (Box 31)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Mill" AR#14 BF0000- Pix, undated (Box 32)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Mill" AR#14 BF0000- Trk, undated (Box 32)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Kids in Library Part 1" AR#15 BG0000- Pix, undated (Box 32)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Kids in Library Part 1" AR#15 BG0000- Trk, undated (Box 32)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Mrs. Hunt, Office AM/PM, Hunt Interview Part 1" AR#10 BB0000- Pix, undated (Box 32)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Mrs. Hunt, Office AM/PM, Hunt Interview Part 1" AR#10 BB0000- Trk, undated (Box 32)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Hunt Interview Part 2" 245.0047, AR#11 BC0000- Pix, undated (Box 32)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Hunt Interview Part 2" 245.0047, AR#11 BC0000- Trk, undated (Box 32)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #4 - I/I-714-8378 - I/I-714-9151, undated (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :60" Original Negative A-Roll, undated (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Progress :60" Original Negative B-Roll, undated (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Spots (Enemies, Who is he fighting for?, Pride) Original Color Negative, A and B Rolls, Also Pulled Shot, undated (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Testimonials - Helms" Track Extensions, undated (Box 33)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Lumber Yard Testimonial, Mechanic and Wife, Young Man" AR#7 AG0000- Trk, undated (Box 34)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Lumber Yard Testimonial, Mechanic and Wife, Young Man" AR#7 AG0000- Pix, undated (Box 34)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Hunt Speech in Auditorium Part 2" Code CF0000 AR#24 Sync Trk, undated (Box 34)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Hunt Speech in Auditorium Part 2" Code CF0000 AR#24 Sync Pix, undated (Box 34)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Porch Couple Part 2" 245.0047 AR#5 AE0000- Pix, undated (Box 34)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "Porch Couple Part 2" 245.0047 AR#5 AE0000- Trk, undated (Box 34)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "General Store" 245.0047 AR#6 AF0000- Pix, undated (Box 34)
  - DHS Films - Hunt - "General Store" 245.0047 AR#6 AF0000- Trk, undated (Box 34)
  - DHS Films - "Hunt" 245.0047 W/S R.18 S0000 Trk., undated (Box 35)
  - DHS Films - "Hunt" R.17 MOS Pix, undated (Box 35)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #9 - U-178-4951 -- U-178-5733, undated (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Spots - "Future," "Motive," A & B Rolls, Original Color Negative, undated (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #9 - U-178-7373 -- U178-8164, undated (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #9 - I/C-132-0356 -- I/C-132-1084, undated (Box 36)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #3 - K-368-2762 -- K-368-3406, undated (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #3 - A-492-5240 -- A-492-5981, undated (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #3 - K-369-0873 -- K-369-1666, undated (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #2 - D-490-0535 -- D-490-1295, undated (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #2 - K-368-4374 -- K-368-5124, undated (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #2 - M-237-6809 -- M-237-7558, undated (Box 37)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #12 - N-121-1816 -- N-121-2613, undated (Box 38)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #12 - U-377-9594 -- U-378-0386, undated (Box 38)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #13 - C/Z-101-1515 -- C/Z-101-2330, undated (Box 38)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #13 - C/Z-101-0729 -- C/Z-101-1531, undated (Box 38)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #13 - U-178-6560 -- U-178-7359, undated (Box 38)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #13 - C/Z-101-3971 -- C/Z-101-4665, undated (Box 38)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #13 - N-121-1009 -- N-121-1794, undated (Box 38)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #13 - U-178-5751 -- U-178-6527, undated (Box 38)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #11 - K-554-2012 -- K-554-2810, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #11 - I/J-590-5502 -- I/J-590-6300, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #11 - I/J-590-7119 -- I/J-590-7919, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #12 - C/Z-101-3158 -- C/Z-101-3957, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #12 - U-378-0407 -- U-378-1198, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #12 - I/J-590-7932 -- I/J-590-8644, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #12 - C/Z-101-2349 -- C/Z-101-2880, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #5 - K-660-3355 -- K-660-3733, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #12 - C/Z-101-2892 -- C/Z-101-3148, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #12 - U-378-1209 -- U378-1624, undated (Box 39)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #5 - M-237-6000 - M237-6795, undated (Box 40)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #5 - D-740-4242 -- D-740-49-59, undated (Box 40)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #8 - L-918-0607 -- L-918-1396, undated (Box 40)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #8 - I/A-933-8092 -- I/A-933-8887, undated (Box 40)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #8 - T/S-984-5253 -- T/S-984-6059, undated (Box 40)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #11 - D-542-2848 -- D-543-3375, undated (Box 40)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #11 - K-551-0348 -- K-551-1036, undated (Box 40)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #11 - K-551-1965 -- K-551-2695, undated (Box 40)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #8 - I/A-933-5681 -- I/A-933-6466, undated (Box 41)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #7 - I/A-933-4863 -- I/A-933-5664, undated (Box 41)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #7 - I/S-984-7692 -- I/S-984-8438, undated (Box 41)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #7 - I/A-933-6476 -- I/A-933-7273, undated (Box 41)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #8 - I/A-933-7384 -- I/A-933-8080, undated (Box 41)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #8 - H-838-4316 -- H-838-4581, undated (Box 41)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #8 - L-917-8993 -- L-917-9586, undated (Box 41)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #7 - K-773-5716 -- K-773-6109, undated (Box 41)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #7 - D-540-6022 -- D-540-6244, undated (Box 41)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #8 - T/S-984-8502 -- T/S-984-9232, undated (Flatbox 42)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #7 - T/S-984-6882 -- T/S-984-7640, undated (Flatbox 42)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #7 - T/S-984-6071 -- T/S-984-6870, undated (Flatbox 42)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #7 - K-773-4976 -- K-773-5759, undated (Flatbox 43)
  - DHS Films - Hunt Can #4 - M-237-5182 -- M-237-5986, undated (Flatbox 43)
- Audiotape, 1976, 1983-1984, 1990-1992, 1996, and undated
  This series contains audio on standard cassettes, minicassettes, microcassettes, and 1/4" open reels. The tapes include radio commercials produced by the Hunt campaign, recordings of speeches and press conferences, and a small number of recordings of opponents' speeches and commercials. Transcripts for some of the Hunt radio commercials may be found in Series 5.
  - Veto power press conference, 1976 June 1 (Box 50)
  - YDC Speeches, O'Henry, Strickland, 1976 December 28 (Box 50)
  - Congressional Club, Workfare Ad #1 from WPTF (slightly slow speed), 1983 January 15 (Box 50)
  - Helms for Senate Ad, fundraising, 1983 March 29 (Box 50)
  - Helms for Senate, 1983 April-May (Box 50)
  - Gas Tax (Pete & Dave) Helms for Senate #6, 1983 May 13 (Box 50)
  - Gas Tax (Pete & Dave) Helms for Senate #6, 1983 May 13 (Box 50)
  - Helms for Senate / Crime Discovery Bill (pulled off) Ad #1, 1983 August 8 (Box 50)
  - Helms Ads flap, 1983 August 8 (Box 50)
  - Helms Senate / Hunt Crime #2, 1983 August 11 (Box 50)
  - Helms for Senate, Crime #3, 1983 August 12 (Box 50)
  - Helms for Denate, "Funny" Discover Law Ad, 1983 August 24 (Box 50)
  - Helms for Senate / Crime 4 & 4-A, 1983 August 24 (Box 50)
  - North Carolina Democratic Party, Middle Class, Social Security, Farmers, JHNC-3001-3, 1983 November 17 (Box 50)
  - North Carolina Democratic Party, NCDP 1001-3-4, 1983 November 22 (Box 50)
  - North Carolina Democratic Party (NCDP) Voting Record, 1983 December 6 (Box 50)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #1, 1984 January 10 (Box 49)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #2, 1984 January 10 (Box 49)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #3, 1984 January 10 (Box 49)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #4, 1984 January 10 (Box 49)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #5, 1984 January 10 (Box 49)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #10, 1984 January 11 (Box 49)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #6, 1984 January 11 (Box 49)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #7, 1984 January 11 (Box 49)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #8, 1984 January 11 (Box 49)
  - D.H.S. Film, "Hunt" Sound Reel #9, 1984 January 11 (Box 49)
  - JHSEN 1001, "Accomplishments;" JHSEN 1002, "Farm Life", 1984 February 9 (Box 50)
  - Speech from Republican Convention, includes Helms speech, quality very poor, 1983 May (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1014, "Facts" Radio :60, 1984 June 19 (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1012, "Death Squads" Radio :60, 1984 June 26 (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1015, "Debate", 1984 July 30 (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1015, "Griffith on Debate", 1984 August 12 (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1017, "Griffith on Debate" revised, 1984 August 13 (Box 50)
  - Bonnie Franklin, Speech for Jim Hunt, 1984 September 21 (Box 50)
  - Bonnie Franklin, Speech for Jim Hunt, 1984 September 21 (Box 50)
  - Bonnie Franklin, Speech for Jim Hunt, 1984 September 21 (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1025, "Sam Perkins on Voter Registration - REVISED;" JHSEN 1026, "Roberta Flack on Voter Registration - REVISED", 1984 September 26 (Box 50)
  - Democratic Party Radio 5 60 second commercials, 1984 October 2 (Box 50)
  - Hunt #1, 1984 October 3 (Box 49)
  - Hunt #2, 1984 October 3 (Box 49)
  - Hunt #3, 1984 October 3 (Box 49)
  - Hunt #4, 1984 October 3 (Box 49)
  - Hunt #5, 1984 October 3 (Box 49)
  - JHSEN 1027, "It's a Lie", 1984 October 4 (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1028, "He Will;" JHSEN 1029, "Network", 1984 October 8 (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1031, "Supreme Court", 1984 October 17 (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1030, "Roberta Flack on Hunt", 1984 October 17 (Box 50)
  - Hunt #6, 1984 October 30 (Box 49)
  - Hunt "Promo" TVP 1036, 1984 October 30 (Box 50)
  - JHSEN 1038, "Your Choice", 1984 October 31 (Box 50)
  - 4th District Gov. '84 Debate, 1984 (Box 50)
  - "The Jesse Helms Record 1984" (floppy blue disc) 4 or 5 anti-Hunt commercials (Box 50)
  - Hunt Radio, 1984 (Box 50)
  - NBPTS N.C./S.C. Forum Banquet, 1990 April 11 (Box 50)
  - NBPTS N.C./S.C. Forum Wrap-Up, 1990 April 12 (Box 50)
  - NBPTS N.C./S.C. Forum Panel Discussion, 1990 April 12 (Box 50)
  - NBPTS N.C./S.C. Forum Lunch, 1990 April 12 (Box 50)
  - Goldsboro Speech [illegible], 1991 September 19 (Box 50)
  - Lexington / Troutman, 1991 October 3 (Box 50)
  - Candidate Forum, Vance-Aycock, 1991 October 12 (Box 50)
  - CCNC Forum, Umstead Park, 1991 November 9 (Box 50)
  - NCAE Endorsement Interview, 1991 November 9 (Box 50)
  - CCNC Forum, Umstead Park, 1991 November 9 (Box 50)
  - Washington, Columbia, Owen's Rest (Dare), Currituck, 1991 November 12 (Box 50)
  - Elizabeth City, Hertford, Plymouth, Grimesland, 1991 November 13 (Box 50)
  - Guilford County / Durham City and County Education / [illegible] Fundraiser / Samet RF, 1991 November-December (Box 50)
  - Macon County, Hendersonville, 1991, 1996 (Box 50)
  - Asheville [illegible], Lake [illegible], 1991, 1996 (Box 50)
  - Clinton Breakfast / Trenton Lunch, 1992 January (Box 50)
  - World Class Schools Forum, 1992 January 11 (Box 50)
  - Gardner Announcement Speech, Kerr-Scott Building - Raleigh, North Carolina, 1992 January 30 (Box 50)
  - Cumberland County Rally / Winston-Salem Fundraiser, 1992 January-February (Box 50)
  - Announcement Speech, Listen and Learn / WPTF Radio, 1992 February 25 (Box 50)
  - Franklin County Breakfast, 1992 February 27 (Box 50)
  - Johnston County [illegible], 1992 March 2 (Box 50)
  - Guilford County Precinct Meetings, 1992 March 5 (Box 50)
  - McDowell County and [illegible] Fundraiser, 1992 March 12 (Box 50)
  - Columbus County Luncheon, 1992 March 19 (Box 50)
  - Onslow County Rally and [illegible] / Greensboro News & Record Editorial Board, 1992 March (Box 50)
  - Martin County Breakfast / Wayne County Rally, 1992 April 14 (Box 50)
  - Hunt Education Paper Press Briefing, North Carolina Democratic Party Headquarters, 1992 April 22 (Box 50)
  - Davidson County Rally / Forsyth County, 1992 April 23 (Box 50)
  - Greensboro Rally, 1992 April 28 (Box 50)
  - Thornburg Crime Press Conference, 1992 April 28 (Box 50)
  - NC Chiropractors Association / Vance County Breakfast, 1992 April (Box 50)
  - Hunt / Sierra Club Meeting, 1992 May 28 (Box 50)
  - BRT Education Workshop (continued), 1992 June 4 (Box 50)